To finish this domain on database design,
let's look at backing up and securing our data.
It is important to make sure a database
is backed up regularly to restore the data
if it is accidentally deleted or changed. Ideally,
a backup should go to a different drive than the
one hosting a database, but for now, let's just
see how a backup is done. I will select and hold
(or right-click) the AdventureWorks database,
select Tasks, and then Back Up. The Back Up
Database window appears. We have two choices for
a backup. We can do a full backup, which backs
up the entire database, or a differential backup,
which backs up all the changes since the last full
backup. If you ever need to restore a database
from a differential backup, you first need to
restore the last full backup and then the most
recent differential backup of the same database.
For this example, we will do a full backup. We
can back this database up to a disk or to a URL,
which would most likely be to a storage area
in Azure. I will use a disk for this example.
I will not run the backup right now, as doing
so would take considerable time, but I wanted
you to see how this is done and emphasize the
importance of backing up a database regularly.